https://www.bowl-america.com/privacy-policy/

Blast Pass
Sign-Up For Our E-Club Now!
PRIVACY POLICY
Bowl America is highly sensitive to the privacy interests of consumers and believes that the protection of those interests is one of its most significant responsibilities. In acknowledgment of its obligations, Bowl America has adopted the following Privacy Policy applicable to information about consumers that it acquires in the course of its business.
TERMS OF USE POLICY
Please read these Terms Of Use Policy (referred to as “the Terms”) carefully before using this site. By using this site, you are agreeing to these Terms. If you do not agree with any of the Terms below, do not use this site. Bowl America Inc. reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, alter or otherwise update these Terms at any time and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates. Regardless of changes in these Terms, personally identifiable information will never be used in ways materially different than stated in these Terms of Use without first providing you a meaningful opportunity to opt-out or prevent that use.
PRIVACY
Bowl America respects the privacy concerns of the visitors to its site on the Internet. As a general policy, no personal information is automatically collected from visitors to our sites. We train all of our employees about the importance of privacy. We give access to information about consumers only to those employees who require it to perform their jobs.  We make access to privacy-sensitive information subject to rigorous procedural and technological controls, consistent with legal requirements and the demands of customer service.  When we make our technology or services available to business partners, we will not share with them any more consumer information than is necessary, and we will make every reasonable effort to assure, by contract or otherwise, that they use our technology and services in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
CHILDREN
Bowl America is committed to protecting the privacy of children. Neither the Company nor any of its services are designed or intended to attract children under the age of 13. We do not collect Personal Information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13. Bowl America makes a special effort to encourage children to consult with their parents before furnishing data. A parent or guardian, however, may use our Web Sites for the benefit of a minor. The parent or guardian is solely responsible for providing supervision and care of the use for the benefit of such minor. The parent or guardian assumes full responsibility for ensuring that any information shared is kept secure and that the information submitted is accurate. The parent or guardian also assumes full responsibility for the interpretation and use of any information or tools provided through us.  Any parent or guardian may review and delete such information by contacting us at Bowl America Inc. 6446 Edsall Road, Alexandria, VA 22312 or by email at administrator@bowl-america.com.
HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION PROVIDED BY VISITORS
Through our site, the information we may receive, including names, email addresses and other information are provided voluntarily by our visitors. This information may be retained by Bowl America Inc. for the purpose in which the information was provided. By electing to receive emails from us, we are providing a requested service.  If at anytime you no longer wish to receive communications from Bowl America, follow the opt out procedure in your email and you will be removed from future mailings.  Bowl America does not sell, trade or rent your name, email address or any other information provided to third parties.  We will provide individually-identifiable information about consumers to third parties only if we are compelled to do so by order of a duly-empowered governmental authority, we have the express permission of the consumer, or it is necessary to process transactions and provide our services.
TRADEMARKS, COPYRIGHTS AND RESTRICTIONS
This site is controlled and operated Bowl America Inc. All materials on this site, including images, illustrations, and video clips, are protected by copyrights which are owned and controlled by Bowl America Inc. or by other parties that have licensed their material to Bowl America Inc. (“Copyrights”). Material from Bowl America Inc. or any of its websites may not be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way. Modification of the materials or use of the materials for any other purpose is a violation of the copyrights and other proprietary rights. For purposes of this Terms of Use Agreement, the use of any such material on any other web site or networked computer environment is prohibited.
CONTACT INFORMATION
This site is controlled and operated by: Bowl America Inc. 6446 Edsall Road Alexandria VA 22312.
Copyright © 2020 Bowl America, Inc.
